{"data":[{"question":"I'm not ________ in hotels.","a":"used to live","b":"use to live","c":"use to living","d":"used to living","answer":"4","explain":"- Be\/get used to Verb_ing\/something: to have experienced something so that it no longer seems surprising, difficult, strange...\n\n- Used to Verb:\n\n+ Expresses the idea that something was an old habit that stopped in the past.\n\n+ Used to talk about past facts or generalizations which are no longer true","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"When she lived in Japan she had to get used ________ raw fish.","a":"to eat","b":"to eating","c":"eat","d":"eating","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Be\/get used to Verb_ing\/something: to have experienced something so that it no longer seems surprising, difficult, strange...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"He often sleeps out in the open. He is used ________ out in the open.","a":"to sleep","b":"to sleeping","c":"of sleeping","d":"of sleep","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Be\/get used to Verb_ing\/something: to have experienced something so that it no longer seems surprising, difficult, strange...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Did you ________ to that place?","a":"use to go","b":"used to go","c":"used to going","d":"use to going","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Used to Verb: \n+ Expresses the idea that something was an old habit that stopped in the past. \n+ Used to talk about past facts or generalizations which are no longer true \n- Interrogative form: Did + S + use to Verb","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"He is not used ________ on the right as we do on the continent.","a":"to driving","b":"drive","c":"to drive","d":"driving","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Be\/get used to Verb_ing\/something: to have experienced something so that it no longer seems surprising, difficult, strange... ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"My girlfriend didn't ________ so much.","a":"used to smoke","b":"use to smoke","c":"use to smoking","d":"used to smoking","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Used to Verb: \n+ Expresses the idea that something was an old habit that stopped in the past. \n+ Used to talk about past facts or generalizations which are no longer true \n- Negative form: S +didn't + use to Verb","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"I am not ________ this cold weather of yours.","a":"use to","b":"used to","c":"use at","d":"used at","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Be used to Verb_ing\/something: to have experienced something so that it no longer seems surprising, difficult, strange... \n- Negative form: be not + used to Verb_ing","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"I'm not ________ long distances.","a":"used to running","b":"use to running","c":"used to run","d":"use to run","answer":"1","explain":"- Be used to Verb_ing\/something: to have experienced something so that it no longer seems surprising, difficult, strange...\n\n- Negative form: be not + used to Verb_ing","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"I am ________ up early in the mornings.","a":"used to getting","b":"use to getting","c":"used to get","d":"use to get","answer":"1","explain":"- Be\/get used to Verb_ing\/something: to have experienced something so that it no longer seems surprising, difficult, strange...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Derek used ________ a lot of black coffee when he was at university.","a":"to drinking","b":"drink","c":"to drink","d":"drinking","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Used to Verb: \n+ Expresses the idea that something was an old habit that stopped in the past. \n+ Used to talk about past facts or generalizations which are no longer true","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"}]}